lingoda.com 2015-02-06

# English courses online | learn English online at Lingoda

Lingoda GmbH (hereinafter referred to as "Lingoda") has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: Lingoda.com. 

  * Your Personal Profile
  * Security measures
  * Communications From The Site
  * Protection of Children’s Information
  * Membership and Registration for a subscription
  * Access To Personal Information
  * Changing or Removing Profile Information
  * Who We Share Your Information With
  * Cookies
  * Web Beacons
  * Quizes and Contests
  * Public Forums
  * Links to other websites
  * Testimonials
  * Refer a friend

###### 1\. Your Personal Profile

When we ask information of you, our primary interest is to provide you with more personalized service. We respect your privacy and do not sell, rent or trade your name or personal details to other organizations except as outlined in this policy. 

###### 2\. Security measures

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

If you ever discover a fraudulent charge from Lingoda on your billing statement, please contact us and you must report it immediately to your credit card provider, in accordance with their standard procedures. 

This site makes use of forums, bulletin boards and chat rooms. Please remember that any information you disclose in these areas becomes public. You should always be cautious about the amount of personal information you give to anyone in this context. 

We also insist on password verification at sign-in to protect against unauthorized access to your personal profile and course history. If you leave the computer unattended without logging out of the site, we log you out automatically after some time has passed. 

Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. 

Despite these security procedures and practices, as is the case with all computer networks connected to the Internet, Lingoda cannot guarantee the security of your personal information or any other information provided over the Internet and will not be responsible for breaches of security. 

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

###### 3\. Communications From The Site

You have the ability to unsubscribe from any email sent from our site at anytime, by simply clicking on the unsubscribe link included at the bottom of each email we send. 

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. 

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. 

###### 4\. Protection of Children’s Information

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. This and all of our websites are general audience sites and not designed or intended to attract children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13, nor do we send them requests for personal information, unless we first obtain permission from that child's parent or legal guardian. 

###### 5\. Membership and Registration for a subscription

Lingoda offers language courses online at competitive prices. To take one of these courses, enjoy a free trial or become a user of our community services, you need to become a member of Lingoda. During registration we collect information such as your name and email address. We also ask for demographic information (such as age and gender) in order for you to create a profile. You may also be asked to supply us with credit card information, so that you can pay for the services you request. This information is encrypted on a secure server. As a member, you will be added to our mailing list to receive occasional emails about service information, special offers, and promotions from Lingoda and other companies within the Easy Languages group of companies. 

###### 6\. Access To Personal Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, amend or delete your personal information by making the change on our member information page, by contacting our Customer Support or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to access your personal information within 30 days. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Note that your free account remains active even if your subscription to our paid services has expired. 

###### 7\. Changing or Removing Profile Information

**Editing your profile.** You may change your profile at any time by updating the My Account page. Your changes will be updated immediately. 

**Deleting or deactivating your profile.** You may delete or deactivate your profile at any time by contacting our Customer Service team. 

**Removal of an unauthorized profile.** If you wish to request the removal of an unauthorized profile you may do so by contacting our Customer Service team. 

###### 8\. Who We Share Your Information With

  * We share your personal information with other companies within the Lingoda group of companies so that these companies can market their products or services to you. For a complete picture of what Lingoda Products and Services are available, please visit www.lingoda.com. The only information we share with other companies within the Lingoda group of companies is your name, age group, email address, and country. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact our Customer Service team. 
  * We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as processing your payment or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information _only as necessary to provide_ these services to us 
  * We may also disclose your personal information 
  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process 
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, 
  * if Lingoda is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, 
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so. 

###### 9\. Cookies

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that we store on your computer's browser or hard drive. We and our partners use cookies to remember personal information when you visit our website. For example, if you choose the view our site in French we will store that information in your cookie so we can show you our site in French the next time you visit. We also use them to store your login ID to make it easier for you to login to our site. Most browsers allow you the option of preventing cookies from being stored on your computer, though doing so will cause you to lose many of the benefits of Lingoda. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. 

We use the service of a third party tracking utility company to track the behavior of visitors to our site. However, we do not have access to or control over their cookies. The information we collect through our third party tracking utility company is completely anonymous and is used to improve our services and marketing efforts. 

As is true of most websites, we gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

###### 10\. Web Beacons

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. 

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. 

In some of our email messages, we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the Lingoda website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination page on our website. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links in the email messages. 

###### 11\. Quizes and Contests

We may provide you the opportunity to participate in quizzes or contests on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these quizzes and contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and email address), and demographic information (such as zip code). 

We may use this information to personalize our communications to you and to suggest more relevant products and services. 

###### 12\. Public Forums

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums.You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

###### 13\. Links to other websites

This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Lingoda is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by the Lingoda website. 

###### 14\. Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to request to have your testimonial removed you contact our Customer Service. 

###### 15\. Refer a friend

If you decide to refer a friend to our site as part of Lingoda contests or other promotions, we ask you for the friend's email address and give you the option of sending them a personal message. Lingoda will then send a one-time, automatically generated email message inviting your friend to visit our site. Lingoda stores the email address in your personal file solely for the purpose of crediting you if your friend becomes a member. Your friend may contact us to request that we remove this information from our database. 

We also utilize an import contacts feature to help you keep in touch with your contacts and other members. We make it easy for you to invite people from your email address books to join you on our Site. At your request we will search your email address book to help you import your contacts to our site. When we do this, we do not store any of your contacts' information our our servers. We may send an email on your behalf to your contacts, but we do not keep their email address or any other information until they register for our site themselves. 

The Lingoda privacy policy is subject to change. If we decide to change the way we collect, use or share information, we will take commercially reasonable steps to notify members by way of an email that explains the changes and gives them the choice as to whether or not we may use their information in the new manner. If you have any questions about this policy statement, or about any of Easy Language's other policies and practices, please contact us. 

Welcome to Lingoda.com, the premier service for people around the world to learn languages online. This agreement (the “Agreement”) represents the entire contract between you and Lingoda GmbH ("Lingoda") with respect to the above mentioned site(s) (the "Site") and, if applicable, the fee-based subscription services therein. By visiting, becoming a customer of, purchasing a gift subscription from, or subscribing to Lingoda, you agree, without qualification, to be bound by the terms and conditions (the “Terms”) of use set out below. 

  1. Acceptance of the Terms
  2. Changes to these Terms
  3. Provision of the Services
  4. Your Rights
  5. Use of the Service
  6. Intellectual Property Rights
  7. Access and Interference
  8. Privacy and Security Policy
  9. Community forums, chats, message boards, and email conduct
  10. Fees and payments
  11. Indemnification
  12. Miscellaneous

###### 1\. Acceptance of the Terms

By using the information, tools, features and functionality located on Lingoda.com (together the "Service" or the "Services"), you agree to be bound by this Agreement and the Terms, whether you are a "Visitor" (which means that you simply browse the Lingoda website) or you are a "Customer" (which means that you have registered with Lingoda). The term "you" or "User" refers to a Visitor or a Customer. The term "we" refers to Lingoda. The term "Material" refers to all class materials used in our classes. If you wish to become a Customer, communicate with other Customers and/or make use of the Service, you must read this Agreement and indicate your acceptance during the registration process. 

If you do not agree with all the Terms, do not use the Site. 

Please review all of the Terms carefully before using the Site. 

By using the Site, you agree to be bound by the Terms and confirm that you are over the age of 13 and able to form legally binding contracts. 

Before you continue, you should print or save a local copy of this Agreement for your records. 

###### 2\. Changes to these Terms

Lingoda has the right to modify this Agreement and any policies affecting or pertaining to the Site. Your continued use of the Site following notice of the Agreement modification will be considered an acceptance of the modified terms and conditions of use. Your recourse upon dissatisfaction with the modified terms of use is to cancel your subscription by following the instructions set out above. Furthermore, Lingoda reserves the right to modify, suspend or discontinue the Site at any time. 

###### 3\. Provision of the Services

In providing the Services, we do not actively monitor the display, transmission and exchange of Material that is accessible by means of the Services, nor do we maintain any obligation to do so except as otherwise determined by us or required by the laws of applicable jurisdictions. However, subject to the terms of our Privacy and Security Policy, we reserve the right to monitor the Services for purposes of determining that their usage is in compliance with these Terms and applicable laws. In addition, and as described elsewhere in these Terms, we maintain an absolute and unconditional right to review and remove Material accessible by or transmitted through the Services that, in our sole discretion, we believe is in violation of the law of these Terms or is unacceptable to us in our sole discretion. 

From time to time and without prior notice to you, we may change, expand and improve the Site and Services. We may also, at any time, cease to continue operating part or all of the Services or selectively disable certain aspects of the Services or portions of the Site. Any modification or elimination of the Services will be done in our sole and absolute discretion and without an ongoing obligation or liability to you, and your use of the Site and Services do not entitle you to the continued provision or availability of the Site and Services. 

###### 4\. Your Rights

Lingoda offers you a non-transferable, non-exclusive, limited right to access, use and display the content of this Site, provided that you comply with this Agreement and the Terms as set out in full. The materials of this Site are provided to you only for your private, non-commercial use. Certain services of this Site are available only to registered customers of Lingoda. 

By electing to purchase a subscription or register for a trial of Lingoda, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions set out below in section 10 in the Lingoda billing policy. 

###### 5\. Use of the Service

Your right to access and use Lingoda.com and the Service is personal to you and is not transferable by you to any other person or entity. You are only entitled to access and use Lingoda for lawful purposes. 

You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your Lingoda account (the "Account"), username and password. You agree to notify Lingoda of any unauthorized use of your Lingoda Account. In order for the Service to function effectively, you must also keep your registration information up to date and accurate. If you do not do this, the accuracy and effectiveness of the Service to you will be affected. 

In our sole and absolute discretion, we may terminate your Account, or modify, reclaim or remove any username associated with your Account, for any reason (including for reasons related to unlawful or unauthorized usage) and we are under no obligation to retain a record of your Account or any data or information that you may have stored by means of the Account and/or the Services. 

Your access and use of Lingoda.com may be interrupted from time to time for any of several reasons, including, without limitation, the malfunction of equipment, periodic updating, maintenance or repair of Lingoda.com or other actions that Lingoda, in its sole discretion, may elect to take. Lingoda is not responsible for any loss resulting from your using any of Easy Language’s services, software, materials, audio or video files, content, or communications. 

###### 6\. Intellectual Property Rights

All materials of Lingoda, including content, text, images, software, audio and video files, documentation, Email English and the Site remain at all time the sole property of Lingoda or its suppliers. Such aforementioned materials are protected under international copyright, trademark and other intellectual property laws. You may not post, distribute, sublicense, translate or reproduce in any way any copyrighted materials, trademarks or other proprietary information without the prior express written consent of Lingoda. 

###### 7\. Access and Interference

You agree that you will not:

  * Use any robot, spider, scraper, deep link or other similar automated data gathering or extraction tools, program, algorithm or methodology to access, acquire, copy or monitor Lingoda.com or any portion of Lingoda.com, without Lingoda’s express written consent, which may be withheld in Lingoda’s sole discretion; 
  * Use or attempt to use any engine, software, tool, agent, or other device or mechanism (including without limitation browsers, spiders, robots, avatars or intelligent agents) to navigate or search Lingoda.com, other than the search engines and search agents available through the Service and other than generally available third-party web browsers (such as Microsoft Explorer); 
  * Post or transmit any file which contains viruses, worms, Trojan horses or any other contaminating or destructive features, or that otherwise interfere with the proper working of Lingoda.com or the Service; 
  * Attempt to decipher, decompile, disassemble, or reverse-engineer any of the software comprising or in any way making up a part of Lingoda.com or the Service. Please be aware that your carrier's normal rates and fees, such as text messaging fees, will apply when accessing Lingoda.com with your portable devices. 

###### 8\. Privacy and Security Policy

Your use of our Site and any personal information or other information about you collected by Lingoda.com through, or in connection with, the Site (other than User Generated Content) is subject to our Privacy and Security Policy. 

As indicated in the Terms, our Site is not designed to attract children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifying information from anyone under the age of 13 unless we first obtain permission from that child's parent or legal guardian. 

For questions about our online privacy and security policy for children please refer to the Privacy and Security Policy. 

###### 9\. Community forums, chats, message boards, and email conduct

Lingoda strives to create a global community of language learners. As such, Lingoda provides users with the ability to post messages, use chat rooms, and find learning resources, such as local language schools and job offers. You are solely responsible for the content of these messages as set out in this Agreement. In addition, by using these services, you agree to not publish, contribute or post any material that: 

  * Contains content that is not original or for which you have not received the prior express written consent of the originator of said material. 
  * Contains objectionable language or is in any way profane, pornographic, sexually explicit, slanderous or libelous. 
  * Attempts to contact a fellow user of Lingoda without explicit solicitation by that user.
  * Violates any viable rules, laws or regulations, or infringes on any rights of any third party.
  * Contains viruses or any other code designed to interrupt, destroy or incapacitate the functionality of any software, hardware or telecommunications. 
  * Is considered "spamming," such as chain letters, junk mail, or other solicitations.
  * Attempts to impersonate another person or breach the security of Lingoda and its users.
  * The opinions and messages posted by users at Lingoda do not reflect and are not representative of the views of Lingoda or its employees, affiliates, suppliers or partners. Lingoda is not responsible for the content of messages sent by users to other users they have located through Easy Languages. 

###### 10\. Fees and payments

You will be required to register and create an account with Lingoda (the "Account") in order to access certain features of the Site and Services. Information gathered through the registration process and information related to your account will be subject to these Terms as well as to our "Privacy and Security Policy". You represent and warrant that you will not create an Account for anyone other than yourself without permission, that all information provided by you when creating an Account is true, accurate and complete, and that you will maintain, at all times, true, accurate and complete information related to your Account. 

Certain materials and functionalities of the Site are available only through the purchase of an online language class package (the "Package"). Pursuant to this Agreement you are responsible for any charges associated with connecting to the Site. Lingoda reserves the right to change the Package fees in effect or institute new fees at any time, upon reasonable notice posted on the site and emailed to current customers. 

By purchasing a Package you agree to be bound to the following terms: 

####### Billing Policies

Lingoda fees are exclusive of any applicable VAT or taxes, interest or installment fees charged by the credit card company, or other fees associated with connecting to the Internet. 

Lingoda guarantees that every credit card transaction you make at Lingoda is 100% secure. If at any time you wish to check on the status of your subscription, please login and visit the “My Account” page in your Login area. 

Your language course contains teacher-led classes. Group classes and private classes are delivered on a "class credit basis", giving you access to the stated amount of group classes and private classes that your language course offers. You can always find current prices of language courses posted in the checkout pages and occasionally in other pages of our website. The exact contents of your language courses are clearly set forth and accessible at all times in the logged-in section of the Site under "My account". 

All language course fees are recurring and non-refundable after your purchase. If you do not cancel your language course before the end of the stated course time, you agree to the automatic extension of your language course for the same time and the same terms. If you do not wish to continue your language course, you have to deactivate your account in the “My Account” page in your login area or give us written (email) notice. 

An exception to the prior paragraph is our 7-day money back guarantee when stated explicitly on the checkout page. Within 7 days after purchase you have the right to cancel your language course by written (email) notice and receive your full money back. 

In addition to the classes included in your language course, you can purchase additional classes. These classes give you the right to take more teacher-led classes. Additional classes, whether group or private, those sessions are delivered on a “class credit basis” over a period of 6 months, this means that if you haven’t used those sessions by the end of 6 months after purchasing the class package, those unused sessions are lost to you and will not be refunded. 

####### Free trial

The free trial is available only to first-time users. 

####### Credit card payments

After initial enrollment, if your credit card expires, is cancelled, is lost, or rendered invalid, your subscription is in danger of termination. You will be contacted and given the opportunity to change your registration data. If your credit card is not successfully recharged and you are not renewed successfully, your subscription will be terminated. 

###### 11\. Indemnification

You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless Lingoda and its affiliates, partners, suppliers, and employees from any and all liability, claims, costs, or damages arising from your use of the Site or your breach of this Agreement and any of the Terms set out herein. 

###### 12\. Miscellaneous

If any portion of this Agreement is deemed unlawful, void or unenforceable by any arbitrator or court of competent jurisdiction, this Agreement as a whole shall not be deemed unlawful, void or unenforceable, but only that portion of this Agreement that is unlawful, void or unenforceable shall be stricken from this Agreement. 

You agree that if Lingoda does not exercise or enforce any legal right or remedy which is contained in the Agreement (or which Lingoda has the benefit of under any applicable law), this will not be taken to be a formal waiver of Lingoda’ rights and that those rights or remedies will still be available to Lingoda. 

All covenants, agreements, representations and warranties made in this Agreement shall survive your acceptance of this Agreement and the termination of this Agreement. 

This Agreement represents the entire understanding and agreement between you and Lingoda regarding the subject matter of the same, and supersedes all other previous agreements. 

If you have any questions about this policy statement, or about any of Lingoda's other policies and practices, please contact us on the contact details laid out on Lingoda.com. 

Lingoda.com and related services are, if not otherwise specifically mentioned, supplied by: 

Lingoda GmbH  
Boxhagener Straße 103  
10245 Berlin, Germany 

Lingoda GmbH (hereinafter referred to as "Lingoda") has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: Lingoda.com. 

  * Your Personal Profile
  * Security measures
  * Communications From The Site
  * Protection of Children’s Information
  * Membership and Registration for a subscription
  * Access To Personal Information
  * Changing or Removing Profile Information
  * Who We Share Your Information With
  * Cookies
  * Web Beacons
  * Quizes and Contests
  * Public Forums
  * Links to other websites
  * Testimonials
  * Refer a friend

###### 1\. Your Personal Profile

When we ask information of you, our primary interest is to provide you with more personalized service. We respect your privacy and do not sell, rent or trade your name or personal details to other organizations except as outlined in this policy. 

###### 2\. Security measures

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

If you ever discover a fraudulent charge from Lingoda on your billing statement, please contact us and you must report it immediately to your credit card provider, in accordance with their standard procedures. 

This site makes use of forums, bulletin boards and chat rooms. Please remember that any information you disclose in these areas becomes public. You should always be cautious about the amount of personal information you give to anyone in this context. 

We also insist on password verification at sign-in to protect against unauthorized access to your personal profile and course history. If you leave the computer unattended without logging out of the site, we log you out automatically after some time has passed. 

Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. 

Despite these security procedures and practices, as is the case with all computer networks connected to the Internet, Lingoda cannot guarantee the security of your personal information or any other information provided over the Internet and will not be responsible for breaches of security. 

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

###### 3\. Communications From The Site

You have the ability to unsubscribe from any email sent from our site at anytime, by simply clicking on the unsubscribe link included at the bottom of each email we send. 

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. 

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. 

###### 4\. Protection of Children’s Information

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. This and all of our websites are general audience sites and not designed or intended to attract children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13, nor do we send them requests for personal information, unless we first obtain permission from that child's parent or legal guardian. 

###### 5\. Membership and Registration for a subscription

Lingoda offers language courses online at competitive prices. To take one of these courses, enjoy a free trial or become a user of our community services, you need to become a member of Lingoda. During registration we collect information such as your name and email address. We also ask for demographic information (such as age and gender) in order for you to create a profile. You may also be asked to supply us with credit card information, so that you can pay for the services you request. This information is encrypted on a secure server. As a member, you will be added to our mailing list to receive occasional emails about service information, special offers, and promotions from Lingoda and other companies within the Easy Languages group of companies. 

###### 6\. Access To Personal Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, amend or delete your personal information by making the change on our member information page, by contacting our Customer Support or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to access your personal information within 30 days. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Note that your free account remains active even if your subscription to our paid services has expired. 

###### 7\. Changing or Removing Profile Information

**Editing your profile.** You may change your profile at any time by updating the My Account page. Your changes will be updated immediately. 

**Deleting or deactivating your profile.** You may delete or deactivate your profile at any time by contacting our Customer Service team. 

**Removal of an unauthorized profile.** If you wish to request the removal of an unauthorized profile you may do so by contacting our Customer Service team. 

###### 8\. Who We Share Your Information With

  * We share your personal information with other companies within the Lingoda group of companies so that these companies can market their products or services to you. For a complete picture of what Lingoda Products and Services are available, please visit www.lingoda.com. The only information we share with other companies within the Lingoda group of companies is your name, age group, email address, and country. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact our Customer Service team. 
  * We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as processing your payment or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information _only as necessary to provide_ these services to us 
  * We may also disclose your personal information 
  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process 
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, 
  * if Lingoda is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, 
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so. 

###### 9\. Cookies

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that we store on your computer's browser or hard drive. We and our partners use cookies to remember personal information when you visit our website. For example, if you choose the view our site in French we will store that information in your cookie so we can show you our site in French the next time you visit. We also use them to store your login ID to make it easier for you to login to our site. Most browsers allow you the option of preventing cookies from being stored on your computer, though doing so will cause you to lose many of the benefits of Lingoda. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. 

We use the service of a third party tracking utility company to track the behavior of visitors to our site. However, we do not have access to or control over their cookies. The information we collect through our third party tracking utility company is completely anonymous and is used to improve our services and marketing efforts. 

As is true of most websites, we gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

###### 10\. Web Beacons

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. 

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. 

In some of our email messages, we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the Lingoda website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination page on our website. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links in the email messages. 

###### 11\. Quizes and Contests

We may provide you the opportunity to participate in quizzes or contests on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these quizzes and contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and email address), and demographic information (such as zip code). 

We may use this information to personalize our communications to you and to suggest more relevant products and services. 

###### 12\. Public Forums

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums.You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

###### 13\. Links to other websites

This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Lingoda is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by the Lingoda website. 

###### 14\. Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to request to have your testimonial removed you contact our Customer Service. 

###### 15\. Refer a friend

If you decide to refer a friend to our site as part of Lingoda contests or other promotions, we ask you for the friend's email address and give you the option of sending them a personal message. Lingoda will then send a one-time, automatically generated email message inviting your friend to visit our site. Lingoda stores the email address in your personal file solely for the purpose of crediting you if your friend becomes a member. Your friend may contact us to request that we remove this information from our database. 

We also utilize an import contacts feature to help you keep in touch with your contacts and other members. We make it easy for you to invite people from your email address books to join you on our Site. At your request we will search your email address book to help you import your contacts to our site. When we do this, we do not store any of your contacts' information our our servers. We may send an email on your behalf to your contacts, but we do not keep their email address or any other information until they register for our site themselves. 

The Lingoda privacy policy is subject to change. If we decide to change the way we collect, use or share information, we will take commercially reasonable steps to notify members by way of an email that explains the changes and gives them the choice as to whether or not we may use their information in the new manner. If you have any questions about this policy statement, or about any of Easy Language's other policies and practices, please contact us.
